mytwitterlovers.com 2011-06-16

# Privacy Policy - Gator Apps

**Privacy Policy**

Here at Gator Apps, we respect your privacy. However, just like anywhere on the web, privacy is not perfect. Therefore, we ask you to understand the following:

**Website Visitors**

Just like when visiting any website, information such as your web browser, operating system, system language, referring site, and the date of each request is sent. These information are, in fact, collected by Gator Apps, and are used in reasons such as understanding how visitors use our site. We may also decide to publish trends of our site usage.

Personally-identifying information such as your Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. This information may be used to prevent abusers, who are violating our Terms of Service. We might also report your IP addresses to authority if you're caught abusing our site.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors may choose to interact and use features which will require us to gather personal-identifying information. The amount and the type of information that is gathered depend on the action. Any visitor may refuse to supply personally-identifying information in any of the cases described in the cases below.

**Cookies**

A cookie on your computer is not something edible. It is a string of information that websites store on a visitor's computer, and the visitor's browser provides the cookie each time the visitor returns to the website. Cookies are used to track visitor's usage of this website, and their preferences, in some cases. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed should set their browser to refuse and deny cookies before using our website. However with cookies disabled, some functions such as logins and our chat, might not work properly.

**Sessions**

Sessions are just like cookies. Every time you visit our site, you get a session id. This session id may be set as a cookie, which will be provided to our site on each visit, or encoded in the URL. This is not used frequently and may not be used at all, in many cases.

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising programs in order to server you ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information, such as the ones described in the "Website Visitors" section described above. They use this information to provide advertisements about goods and services of your interest. Google is one of the advertising programs which uses cookie to serve ads on our site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to you based on your previous visits on sites with Google ads. Users may chose to opt out of the use of DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any changes in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.
